story,
single place.
This is a really simple one,
but it's really powerful,
which is when you write things, put
all of the things that you write in
one place.
And then if you put all the things
that you write in one place, well,
normally when I do this, I'm going
to have got an audience, I get them
to do some writing.
It seemed a bit weird for me to
kind of pause and do some writing
tonight. But when I do the show, and
what I do is I get them to do some
writing and then I get them to
review what they've written.
And the idea of putting everything
in one place or two places if you've
got things that you've physically
written and things that you've kind of
written electronically, the idea of
doing that is that when you do get
stuck, when you come back to it, it
will be there, you'll know where it
is to pick it up again. And so I
got stuck for six years, but I still
managed to pick up what I'd written
because I was reasonably good at
putting everything that I've written
in one place. I've recently kind of
collected all my diaries together
which weren't all in one place but
when I did collect them together one
of the things that happened was I
got this insight about having sulked
for six years which I wouldn't have
really figured out if it hadn't
been for looking at the diaries.
So yes it sounds relatively
straightforward and it is kind of very
powerful is to put
everything in a single place.